{
    "id": "f2f3f683278149a0ab40c7cadfe00d83",
    "title": "English Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "His grandfather …………………….. the business many decades ago.",
            "description": "Founded is the past tense of found. To found something is to establish it.",
            "answers": [
                "found",
                "founded",
                "fount"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "823fa303be794f5786ec5d54d5cef8bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ship ……………………… during a hurricane.",
            "description": "To founder is to sink.",
            "answers": [
                "founded",
                "foundered",
                "founted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2cc43b8cb24346ebb88462e3a6234961"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t be …………………………… when I ask you to do something.",
            "description": "Fractious means irritable or cross.",
            "answers": [
                "fastidious",
                "frictional",
                "fractious"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c768df5f91ae4c69a67d9c861580d469"
        },
        {
            "question": "One more …………………………. and you are out of the basketball game.",
            "description": "Foul can refer to something that is against the rules.",
            "answers": [
                "foul",
                "fowl"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c78e5c3e887649399e5283fb35a00037"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is that creature? It is neither fish nor ………………………",
            "description": "A fowl is a chicken or a related bird.",
            "answers": [
                "foul",
                "fowl"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1db33cb7f8594fb1b683283776d8293c"
        },
        {
            "question": "One learns a lot during the ………………………. years of adolescence.",
            "description": "Formative means impressionable.",
            "answers": [
                "formal",
                "former",
                "formative"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "512c30cff92d4ecb87bcbc580253fb8b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ……………………………. head of a large shopping complex.",
            "description": "Formerly means at one time.",
            "answers": [
                "former",
                "formerly",
                "formally"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "17df8b17763d44dba11f773bda5e8ded"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was dressed too …………………….",
            "description": "Formally means in a formal manner.",
            "answers": [
                "formally",
                "formerly",
                "formaly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d92fe378ae494e00917b7d504dd9b1c3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He can play classical and pop but his real ………………………… is jazz improvisation.",
            "description": "Forte means strong point.",
            "answers": [
                "fort",
                "forte",
                "fortee"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "538d2157d03a4de78a7a6b37380fc586"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t ask his opinion unless you are ready for a …………………………… answer.",
            "description": "Forthright means frank.",
            "answers": [
                "forthright",
                "forthcoming",
                "forthrightly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2657b064861243b5ba732ca9e3a06882"
        },
        {
            "question": "Financial assistance from his parents is always …………………………",
            "description": "Forthcoming means ready as needed.",
            "answers": [
                "forthcoming",
                "forthright",
                "forecoming"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f6335dcf342a41e3a3f4267c3774975f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has ………………………… our appointment.",
            "description": "The past participle of forget can be forgot or forgotten. ",
            "answers": [
                "forgot",
                "forgotten",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b5ef3accf07f432d834b0daa6ce30a6e"
        }
    ]
}